oneneighborhood.org 2012-10-02

# One Neighborhood | OneNeighborhood | Philadelphia homelessness | Philly Homeless

**1.        ****What this Privacy Policy Covers  
**

  * This policy covers how OneNeighborhood treats personal information that OneNeighborhood collects and receives including information related to your use of the website.  Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

  * This policy does not apply to the practices of agencies that OneNeighborhood does not own or control or to people that OneNeighborhood does not employ or manage.

**2.        ****Information Collection and Use  
**

  * OneNeighborhood collects personal and agency information when you register with OneNeighborhood.

  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, telephone number, zip code, occupation, employment and personal interests.  Once you register with OneNeighborhood and use our services, you are not anonymous to us.

  * OneNeighborhood records information that you have submitted as a registered user to public and private areas of the website, including comments, posts, documents and weblinks.

  * OneNeighborhood automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request.

**3.        Information Sharing and Disclosure  
**

  * OneNeighborhood does not rent, sell or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated agencies except to provide services you have requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
    * We may provide information to trusted partners who work on behalf of OneNeighborhood under confidentiality agreements.  These agencies do not have any independent right to share this information unless explicitly granted by you to them directly.
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against claims;
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of OneNeighborhood’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
    * OneNeighborhood displays information that you have submitted in private and public areas of the website, as well as agency information for registered agencies, and usernames and dates and times of submission.

**4.        ****Cookies  
**

  * OneNeighborhood may set and access cookies on your computer.

**5.        ****Your ability to edit and delete your account information and preferences.  
**

  * You can edit you user account or agency account information or notification preferences at any time.
  * New content is contributed by users at any time.  Users can opt out of receiving future alerts of new content or by following the instructions contained in the messages they receive.
  * We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the services OneNeighborhood provides, such as service announcements, administrative messages and updates, that are considered part of your OneNeighborhood account without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.
  * You can delete your OneNeighborhood account by visiting our account deletion page.  Past records of your personal or agency information and website use will remain in our archives after your account has been deleted.

**6.        ****Confidentiality and Security  
**

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide services to you or in order to do their jobs.
  * We have physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in place to protect personal information about you.

**7.        ****Changes to this Policy  
**

  * OneNeighborhood may update this policy at any time.  We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your OneNeighborhood account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

**8.        ****Questions and Suggestions  
**

  * If you have any questions or suggestions please contact [hello@oneneighborhood.org](mailto:hello@oneneighborhood.org).
